A Guide to the Cary Reich papers FA1275
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Interview Transcripts and Subject Files, undated; 1; 12 Cubic Feet
  - Wilma Rogalin Interview (Box 5, Folder 201)
  - Corbett Interview (Box 5, Folder 202)
  - Alton Marshall, Interview 8 (Box 5, Folder 203)
  - Al Abrams Interview (Albany) (Box 5, Folder 204)
  - Edward Teller Interview (Box 5, Folder 205)
  - Sheldon Stark Interview (Box 5, Folder 206)
  - Guy Graves Interview (Box 5, Folder 207)
  - Charles Lanigan Interview (Box 5, Folder 208)
  - Henry Kissinger, Interview 1 (Box 5, Folder 209)
  - Margaretta (Happy) Rockefeller, Interview 3 (Box 12, Folder 210)
  - Margaretta (Happy) Rockefeller, Interview 3 (Box 12, Folder 210a)
  - Margaretta (Happy) Rockefeller, Interview 4 (Box 12, Folder 211)
  - Margaretta (Happy) Rockefeller, Interview 4 (Box 12, Folder 211a)
  - Stuart Spencer Interview (Box 5, Folder 212)
  - William Rusher Interview (Box 5, Folder 213)
  - John Deardourff Interview (Box 5, Folder 214)
  - Arnold Fisher Interview (Box 5, Folder 215)
  - Richard Dunham, Interview 2 (Box 5, Folder 216)
  - Daniel Patrick Mahoney Interview (Box 5, Folder 217)
  - George Humphreys Interview (Box 5, Folder 218)
  - Samuel Lefrak Interview (Box 5, Folder 219)
  - Moses Weinstein Interview (Box 5, Folder 220)
  - Joseph McGovern Interview (Box 5, Folder 221)
  - Perry Duryea Interview (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Richard Dunham Interview (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Al Roberts Interview (Box 6, Folder 224)
  - Robert M. Morgenthau Interview, 20 pages (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Harold Jerry Interview (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Irwin Miller Interview (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Edwin Schwenk Interviews (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - Paul Nitze Interview (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Herbert Brownell Interview (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - Joseph Margiotta, Interview 2 (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - Raymond Schaffer Interview (Box 6, Folder 232)
  - Arthur Taylor Interview (Box 6, Folder 233)
  - Hugh Carey Interview (Box 6, Folder 234)
  - Phil Donahue Show, Nelson Rockefeller appearance - Show No. 11178 (Box 6, Folder 235)
  - Edward Kresky interview - III (Box 6, Folder 236)
  - Henry Diamond Interview - II (Box 11, Folder 237)
  - Robert Curcio Interview (Box 6, Folder 238)
  - Joseph Crangle Interview (Box 6, Folder 239)
  - Charles Percy Interviews (Box 6, Folder 240)
  - Matthew Troy Interview (Box 6, Folder 241)
  - William Vanden Heuvel Interview (Box 6, Folder 242)
  - Ernest Curto Interview (Box 6, Folder 243)
  - Alton Marshall Interview - X (Box 6, Folder 244)
  - Albert Hausbeck Interview (Box 6, Folder 245)
  - Phelan Interview (Box 6, Folder 246)
  - William Seidman Interview (Box 6, Folder 247)
  - Charles Webb Interviews - II (Box 6, Folder 248)
  - Charles Webb Interview (Box 6, Folder 249)
  - William Dietel Interview (Box 6, Folder 250)
  - Alan Miller Interview (Box 6, Folder 251)
  - Albert Bowker Interview (Box 6, Folder 252)
  - Donald Button Interview (Box 6, Folder 253)
  - Oscar Lanford Interview (Box 6, Folder 254)
  - John Deardourff Interview (Box 6, Folder 255)
  - John Kingston Interview (Box 6, Folder 256)
  - Paul Belica Interview (Box 6, Folder 257)
  - Robert Douglass Interview - II (Box 11, Folder 258)
  - Gerald Ford Interview (Box 6, Folder 259)
  - David Rockefeller Interview - III (Box 11, Folder 260)
  - David Rockefeller Interview - III (Box 11, Folder 260a)
  - David Rockefeller, Jr. Interview (Box 11, Folder 261)
  - Peter Paine Interview (Box 6, Folder 262)
  - Robert Douglass Interview (Box 11, Folder 263)
  - Daniel Patrick Moynihan Interview (Box 6, Folder 264)
  - Charles Rangel Interview (Box 6, Folder 265)
  - Stephen Hopkins Interview (Box 6, Folder 266)
  - Correspondence and Notes, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 267)
  - Hugh Morrow Interview with Kenneth Riland and other files (Box 12, Folder 268)
  - Moses Weinstein Interview (Box 6, Folder 269)
  - Victor Gotbaum Interview (Box 7, Folder 270)
  - Robert Armao Interview (Box 7, Folder 271)
  - Henry Kissinger Interview - II (Box 7, Folder 272)
  - Roswell Perkins Interview - IV (Box 7, Folder 273)
  - Ann Hevesi Interview (Box 7, Folder 274)
  - John Marchi Interview (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - Clifton Wharton Interview (Box 7, Folder 276)
  - Sylvester (Pat) Weaver Interview (Box 7, Folder 277)
  - James Emery Interview (Box 7, Folder 278)
  - Jonathan Moore Interview (Box 7, Folder 279)
  - Margaretta (Happy) Rockefeller, Interview 5 (Box 12, Folder 280)
  - Margaretta (Happy) Rockefeller, Interview 5 (Box 12, Folder 280a)
  - Enid Feist Interview (Box 7, Folder 281)
  - Oscar Ruebhausen Interview - III (Box 7, Folder 282)
  - Jack Germond Interview (Box 7, Folder 283)
  - Barry Van Lare Interview (Box 7, Folder 284)
  - Richard Parsons Interview (Box 7, Folder 285)
  - Donald Zimmerman Interview (Box 7, Folder 286)
  - John Byron Interview (Box 7, Folder 287)
  - John Egan Interview (Box 7, Folder 288)
  - Michael Whiteman Interview (Box 7, Folder 289)
  - Charles Urstadt Interview (Box 7, Folder 290)
  - John Sears Interview (Box 7, Folder 291)
  - Percy Sutton Interview (Box 7, Folder 292)
  - James Casberry Interview (Box 7, Folder 293)
  - Peter Wallison Interview (Box 7, Folder 294)
  - Mark Rockefeller Interview (Box 12, Folder 295)
  - James Wallis Interview (Box 7, Folder 296)
  - David Belin Interview (Box 7, Folder 297)
  - Roger Hooker Interview (Box 7, Folder 298)
  - Rodman Rockefeller, Interview 2 (Box 12, Folder 299)
    Oldest child of Nelson and Mary Clark Rockefeller. Ran the International Basic Economy Corporation after his father divested his interest upon becoming the governor of New York.
  - Rodman Rockefeller, Interview 2 (Box 12, Folder 299a)
  - Richard Aldrich Interview (Box 7, Folder 300)
  - Endicott Peabody Interview (Box 7, Folder 301)
  - William Bagley (Review) Interview (Box 7, Folder 302)
  - Wyatt Tee Walker Interview (Box 7, Folder 303)
  - William Brinton Interview (Box 7, Folder 304)
  - Peter Ogden Interview (Box 7, Folder 305)
  - Lou Levine Interview (Box 7, Folder 306)
  - Jay Coral - Telephone Interview (Box 7, Folder 307)
  - Gary Lee - Telephone Interview (Box 7, Folder 308)
  - John Love Telephone Interview (Box 7, Folder 308A)
  - Donal O'Brien, Jr. Interview (Box 12, Folder 309)
  - Donal O'Brien, Jr. Interview (Box 12, Folder 309a)
  - James Kiepper Interview (Box 7, Folder 310)
  - Richard Stewart Interview (Box 7, Folder 311)
  - Jack Vandervourt Interview - II (Box 7, Folder 312)
  - Senator John D. (Jay) Rockefeller IV Interview (Box 12, Folder 313)
    Nephew of Nelson Rockefeller
  - Harold Haskell Interview (Box 7, Folder 314)
  - Arthur Richardson Interview (Box 7, Folder 315)
  - Stephen Berger Interview (Box 7, Folder 316)
  - Donald Rumsfeld, Interview 2 (Box 7, Folder 317)
  - Thomas Rosenberg Interview (Box 7, Folder 318)
  - Robert Hartmann Interview (Box 7, Folder 319)
  - Warren Weaver Interview (Box 7, Folder 320)
  - Thomas Laverne Interview (Box 8, Folder 321)
  - Vincent ToPany Interview (Box 8, Folder 322)
  - Mildred Mattaheda Interview (Box 8, Folder 323)
  - James Cannon Interview - II (Box 8, Folder 324)
  - Fergus Reid Interview (Box 8, Folder 325)
  - Edward Logue Interview (Box 8, Folder 326)
  - William Kintner Interview (Box 8, Folder 327)
  - Ogden Reid Interview (Box 8, Folder 328)
  - Harold Albright Interview - III (Box 8, Folder 329)
  - Lawrence Murray Interview (Box 8, Folder 330)
  - Levitch and Lightfoot Interview (Box 8, Folder 331)
  - Robert Stone Interview (Box 8, Folder 332)
  - John Hightower Interview (Box 8, Folder 333)
  - Ted Parker Interview (Box 8, Folder 334)
  - Lois Wilson Interview (Box 8, Folder 335)
  - Abby Milton O'Neill Interview (Box 12, Folder 336)
  - Abby Milton O'Neill Interview (Box 12, Folder 336a)
  - Michael Scelsi Interview (Box 8, Folder 337)
  - Dorothy Miller Interview (Box 8, Folder 338)
  - Laurence Roberts Interview (Box 8, Folder 339)
  - J. Richardson Dilworth Interview (Box 12, Folder 340)
  - J. Richardson Dilworth Interview (Box 12, Folder 340a)
  - Barber Conable Interview (Box 8, Folder 341)
  - Peter Berle Interview (Box 8, Folder 342)
  - Martin Ives Interview (Box 8, Folder 343)
  - George Gilder Interview (Box 8, Folder 344)
  - Ernest Boyer Interview (Box 8, Folder 345)
  - Elizabeth Corning Interview (Box 8, Folder 346)
  - Ray Schuler Interview (Box 8, Folder 347)
  - John Gardner Telephone Interview (Box 8, Folder 348)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign, 4 folders (Box 8, Folder 349-352)
  - State Liquor Authority - Liquor Scandal, 3 folders (Box 8, Folder 353-355)
  - Morhouse - State Liquor Authority (Box 8, Folder 356)
  - Morhouse - State Liquor Authority (Box 9, Folder 357-359)
  - Charles Mathias Interview (Box 9, Folder 360)
  - Jason Gettinger Interview (Box 9, Folder 361)
  - Sol Neil Corbin Interview - II (Box 9, Folder 362)
  - Subject Files, 2 folders (Box 9, Folder 363-364)
  - New York Governor, 2 folders (Box 9, Folder 365-366)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) Interviews, 3 folders (Box 9, Folder 367-369)
    Nelson Rockefeller created IBEC in 1947 to promote "basic ecomonomies" in developing countries and thus encourage others in those countries to establish competitive businesses. Rockefeller served as president of IBEC until 1958, when he resigned to assume his duties as Governor of New York.
  - M. L. Whitney Interview (Box 9, Folder 370)
  - Anne-Marie Rasmussen Interview (CLOSED FOLDER) (Box 12, Folder 371)
  - Margaretta (Happy) Rockefeller (Box 9, Folder 372-373)
  - Children (Box 9, Folder 374)
  - Governor (Box 9, Folder 375-377)
  - Governor (Box 10, Folder 378-379)
  - Special Studies, 2 folders (Box 10, Folder 380-381)
  - 1964 Presidential Campaign, 4 folders (Box 10, Folder 382-385)
  - Indexes (Box 10, Folder 386)
  - Letters and Interviews (Box 10, Folder 387)
  - Ballentyne Interview (Box 10, Folder 388)
  - Interview People (Box 10, Folder 389)
  - Hecksher Interview (Box 10, Folder 390)
  - Vice Presidency, 5 folders (Box 10, Folder 391-395)
- Oral History Audio, circa 1980s (Bulk: 1982); 2
  This series consists of audiotaped interviews conducted by author Cary Reich for the first volume, and anticipated second volume, of "The Life of Nelson A. Rockefeller." Additionally, there are partial audiotaped interviews for Reich's "New York Times" expose "The Creative Mind: The Innovator," from April 21, 1985, as well as for other financial articles by Reich.
  Lastly, the series contains audio interviews conducted by Patricia Linden for a "Town and Country" magazine article ("Rockefellers' Monumental Legacy," September 1982) that highlights the Rockefeller legacy in New York. She was also working on her own unrealized, unauthorized biography of Nelson Rockefeller.
  Sound recordings
  - A-B, 2.1
    - Abramovitz, Max, 1982 September 28; Sound, 279 minutes; 1/4 audio cassette (Tape AV 9446)
      Access copy available.
      Interview. Abramovitz was an architect and business partner of Wallace Harrison. Interview with Abramovitz ends at 93 minutes, 52 seconds. Tape then contains partial interview with two unidentified individuals until tape ends at 233 minutes.
    - Abrams, Al, circa1980s; Sound, 244 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9447)
      Interview. Abrams worked on Nelson Rockefeller's campaigns for the Republican presidential nomination in 1964 and 1968.
    - Adams, Sherman, 1982 September 21-22; Sound, 261 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9448)
      Interview. Adams was White House Chief of Staff during President Dwight D. Eisenhower's administration. He had previously served as Governor of New Hampshire. Adams interview ends at 242 minutes, 39 seconds. Tape then contains partial interview with woman identified as Mary Lou until end.
    - Albright, Harry - Part 1, circa1980s; Sound, 318 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9449)
      Interview. Albright was an aide to Nelson Rockefeller, 1967-1975. During Rockefeller's governorship, Albright held various positions, including deputy secretary, executive secretary, and appointments officer. He was also state banking superintendent, 1972-1974. He then served has Rockefeller's special counsel when Rockefeller was Vice President.
    - Albright, Harry - Part 2, circa1980s; Sound, 48 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9450)
    - Alcorn, Meade, 1982 October 4; October 27 1982; Sound, 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9451)
      Interview. Alcorn was a Dartmouth classmate of Nelson Rockefeller and Republican National Chairman.
    - Aldrich, Alexander, 1982 November 15; Sound, 43 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9452)
      Interview. Aldrich was a cousin and gubernatorial aide.
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Loud buzz and low volume throughout tape. Pitch is too fast.
    - Aldrich, Richard - Part 1, 1982 November 16; Sound, 137 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9453)
      Interview. Aldrich was a cousin and IBEC aide.
    - Aldrich, Richard - Part 2, circa1980s; 1/4 inch audio cassette; Sound, 94 minutes (Tape AV 9487)
      Interview. Aldrich was a cousin and IBEC aide. Aldrich interview ends at 57 minutes, 30 seconds. Tape then contains partial interviews with two unidentified individuals until end.
    - Aldrich, Sam, circa1980s; Sound, 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9454)
      Interview. Aldrich was a cousin and Governor Rockefeller's special assistant on race relations.
    - Anderson, Warren, circa1980s; Sound, 133 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9455)
      Interview. Anderson was a New York State Senator.
    - Andre, James, circa1980s; Sound, 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9456)
      Interview. Andre was a New York State Republican committee chair and then Clinton County Republican chair. He previously was a state trooper and worked security at the State House in Albany. Andre interview ends at 86 minutes, 26 seconds. Tape then contains partial interview with Paul Volker until end. Volcker was an economist for the Federal Reserve Bank of New York (1952-1957) and then at Chase Manhattan Bank (1957-1962). He was later Chair of the U.S. Federal Reserve from 1979 to 1987.
    - Armao, Robert, circa1980s; Sound, 93 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9457)
      Interview. Armao was a labor relations aide. Armao interview ends at 71 minutes, 14 seconds. Tape then contains partial interview with Dan Mahoney until end. Mahoney helped found the New York Conservative Party in 1962.
    - Arndt, Willis, 1984 October 4; Sound, 111 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9458)
      Interview. Arndt was an IBEC aide. No aduio for the first 30 minutes, 17 seconds.
    - Aurelio, Richard, circa1980s; Sound, 198 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9459)
      Interview. Aurelio was a journalist and campaign manager for New York City Mayor John Lindsay in 1969. Aurelio interview ends at 143 minutes, 36 seconds. Tape then contains partial interview with unidentified Beth Moore until end. Moore was chairman of the board of the State University of New York and friend of Nelson Rockefeller.
    - Bagley, Harry, circa1980s; Sound, 71 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9460)
      Interview. Bagley was an AIA-IBEC aide.
    - Barclay, Douglas, circa1980s; Sound, 65 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9461)
      Interview. Barclay was a New York State senator.
    - Barnes, Janet, 1972; Sound, 46 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9462)
      Interview. Interview ends at 30 minutes, 15 seconds. Remainder of tape is blank.
      Sound is extremely muffled and sometimes unintelligible.
    - Beichman, Arnold, circa1980s; Sound, 63 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9463)
      Interview. Beichman was a journalist. Interview with Beichman starts at 8 minutes.
    - Belica, Paul, circa1980s; Sound, 64 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9464)
      Interview. Belica was the executive director of the New York State Housing Finance Agency.
    - Belin, David, circa1980s; Sound, 62 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9465)
      Interview. Belin was an attorney for the Rockefeller Commission.
    - Bennett, Robert, circa1980s; Sound, 95 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9466)
      Interview. Bennett was superintendent of the Executive Mansion. Interview ends at 84 minutes, 24 seconds. Remainder of tape is blank.
      Clicking starts around 48 minutes and continues for remainder of tape.
    - Berle, Peter, circa 1980s; 1/4 inch audio cassette; Sound, 62 minutes (Tape AV 15675)
      Interview. Berle was a Democratic New York State Assemblyman, 1969-1974. He was the son of Adolf Augustus Berle, Jr. and Dr. Beatrice Berle. As a freshman assemblyman, he successfully sued then Governor Nelson Rockefeller over budgetary process issues.
    - Berger, Stephen - Part 1, circa1980s; Sound, 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9467)
      Interview. Berger was executive director of the Scott Commission, 1972-1973, and a consultant to the Rockefeller Commission on Critical Choices for Americans, 1973-1974. He was also executive director of the New York Emergency Control Board for the City of New York. Berger interview ends at 47 minutes. Tape then contains interivew with Arthur Richardson until end. Richardson was a campaign aide to Nelson Rockefeller.
    - Berger, Stephen - Part 2, circa1980s; Sound, 11 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9703)
      Interview. Berger was executive director of the Scott Commission, 1972-1973, and a consultant to the Rockefeller Commission on Critical Choices for Americans, 1973-1974. He was also executive director of the New York Emergency Control Board for the City of New York.
    - Bigel, Jack, circa1980s; Sound, 70 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9468)
      Interview. Bigel was a labor union consultant and negotiator.
    - Bixby, Burdell, circa1980s; Sound, 252 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9469)
      Interview. Bixby was chairman of the New York State Thruway Authority, 1960-1970, and managed Governor Nelson Rockefeller's re-election campaign in 1970. Bixby interview ends at 31 minutes, 20 seconds. Tape continues with interview with Dorothy Miller. Miller was a curator at the Museum of Modern Art and a consulatant and curator for numerous art projects for the Rockefeller family. Miller interview ends at 63 minutes. Tape continues with interview with Bixby. Bixby interview ends at 105 minutes, 20 seconds. Tape continues with interview with William Alton. Alton was a friend and IBEC aide. Alton interview ends at 107 minutes, 37 seconds. Tape continues with interviews with multiple unidentified individuals until 157 minutes, 17 seconds. Tape continues with interview with Bixby until end.
    - Bolton, Lee, circa1980s; Sound, 61 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9471)
      Interview with art photographer Lee Bolton. Collaborated with Nelson Rockefeller in the 1970s on art book projects.
    - Bowker, Albert, circa1980s; Sound, 95 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9472)
      Interview. Bowker was chancellor of the City University of New York and then the University of California, Berkeley. Bowker interview ends at 65 minutes, 52 seconds. Tape then contains partial interview with Charles Webb until end. Webb was counsel to New York State Assemblyman Perry Duryea and worked on the reapportionment of legislature districts.
    - Boyd, Joe, circa1980s; Sound, 93 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9473)
      Interview with Joseph Boyd, Governor Nelson Rockefeller's Congressional liaison officer in Washington, DC. Boyd also served as the Governor's liaison to the New York State legislature.
    - Boyer, Ernest, circa1980s; Sound, 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9474)
      Interview. Boyer was chancellor of the State University of New York system.
    - Braden, Joan, circa1980s; Sound, 189 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9475)
      Interview. Braden was a friend of Nelson Rockefeller and a Rockefeller family aide. Braden interview ends at 132 minutes, 54 seconds. Tape then contains partial interview with George Shapiro until end. Shapiro was counsel to New York Governor Thomas Dewey.
    - Braden, Tom, circa1980s; Sound, 142 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9476)
      Interview. Braden was a friend and family aide. Braden interview ends at 118 minutes, 44 seconds. Tape then contains partial interview with Rodman Rockefeller until end. Rodman Rockefeller was the son of Nelson Rockefeller. He was vice president of the International Basic Economy Corporation, 1968 to 1972, and its chief executive, 1972 to 1980.
    - Brinton, William, circa1980s; Sound, 89 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9477)
      Interview. Brinton was national chairman for the Draft Rockefeller movement. Tape begins with partial interview with Josh Friedman. Friedman was a reporter for the New York Post. Brinton interview begins at 5 minutes, 18 seconds and ends at 27 minutes, 48 seconds. Tape continues with interview with Friedman until end.
    - Bronston, Jack, circa1980s; Sound, 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9478)
      Interview. Bronston was a New York State senator.
    - Brown, Richard A., circa1980s; Sound, 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9479)
      Interview. Richard A. Brown was the legislative representative for New York City, 1970-1973. Brown interview ends at 87 minutes, 22 seconds. Tape then contains partial interview with William Golub until end. Golub was an attorney who was special assistant to Governor Nelson Rockefeller for rail and commuter problems. He was also special consultant to the Moreland Act Commission to draft legislation that created sweeping changes in New York State's liquor laws.
    - Brownell, Herbert, circa1980s; Sound, 85 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9480)
      Interview. Brownell was United States Attorney General, 1953-1957.
    - Bruno, Joseph, circa1980s; Sound, 94 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9481)
      Interview. Bruno was a campaign aide.
    - Buckley, Jr., William F., circa1980s; Sound, 95 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9482)
      Interview. Buckley was the founder of National Review magazine. Interview starts at 5 minutes and ends at 21 minutes. Tape then contains partial interview with Evelyn Cunningham until end. Cunningham was a reporter for the Pittsburgh Courier in its Harlem office and then special assistant to Governor Nelson Rockefeller. She was appointed director of the Women's Unit within the Governor's Office.
    - Burbank, Kershaw, circa1980s; Sound, 181 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9483)
      Interview. Burbank was a campaign and family aide.
    - Burns, John, circa1980s; Sound, 51 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9484)
      Interview. Burns was New York State Democratic chairman.
    - Button, Daniel, circa1980s; Sound, 47 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9485)
      Interview. Button was assistant to the president of the State University of New York, 1952-1958; executive editor of the Albany Times Union newspaper, 1960-1966; and a Republican member of the United States House of Representatvies, 1967-1971.
    - Byron, John, circa1980s; Sound, 82 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9486)
      Interview. Byron was director of construction of the South Mall for the State Office of General Services, an agency Governor Nelson Rockefeller created to oversee the project.
  - C-D, 2.2
    - Cain, Edward, circa1980s; Sound, 83 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9487)
      Interview. Cain was chairman of the Genesee County Republican Committee.
    - Callan, Albert and Virginia, circa1980s; Sound, 141 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Tape AV 9488)